<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<language id="44">
<page id="17" title="Boardcomp. objects" descr="">
 <t id="3501">Corporate Sector Shipyard</t>
 <t id="3502">{17,3108} {17,3509}</t>
 <t id="3591">Corporate Sector Space Equipment Dock</t>
 <t id="3592">Corporate Sector Space Equipment Docks are basically functional but not built for comfort, they are solely built to upgrade space vehicles.</t>
 <t id="20381">Corporate Sector Stock Exchange</t>
</page>
<page id="8385" title="Litcube's Revelation" descr="Texts" voice="yes">
 <t id="1">Litcube's Revelation</t>
 <t id="2">[author][red]%s[/red][/author]FLASH %sZ\n\nTO ALL REACHABLE PARTIES\n\nOCV RECON ELEMENTS DETECTED IN [red]%s[/red].\n\nALL CIVILIAN CRAFTS AND GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS SHOULD REPORT\nTO DESIGNATED EVACUATION ZONES AND AWAIT FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS.\n\nTO ALL MILITARY FORCES AND CAPABLE CIVILIAN VOLUNTEERS:\nOCV ARE ASSUMING PRELUDE TO ASSAULT FROM %s.\nVOLUNTEERS WILL BE STIPULATED PER OCV ELIMINATION.</t>
 <t id="3">[author][green]%s[/green][/author]FLASH %sZ\n\nTO ALL REACHABLE PARTIES\n\nOCV CRAFT HAVE ELIMINATED PRIMARY DEFENSIVE FORCES OVER %s.\n\n\nCONTIGENCY PLAN IS NOW IN EFFECT. WITHDRAW ALL UNITS FROM %s IMMEDIATELY AND RETURN TO NEARBY MILITARY OUTPOSTS AND SHIPYARDS FOR REFIT AND REPAIRS.\n\nCIVILIANS ARE ADVISED TO VOLUNTEER TO SUPPORT DEFENSES IN THE CASE OF ANOTHER ATTACK.\n\nSTAND BY FOR FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS.\n</t>
 <t id="4">[author][green]%s[/green][/author]FLASH %sZ\n\nTO ALL REACHABLE PARTIES\n\nOCV INFASTRUCTURE ABOVE %s HAS BEEN CONFIRMED TO BE DESTROYED.\n\nIMMEDIATE DISPATCH OF %s REGULAR MILITARY FORCES TO GARRISON %s HAS BEEN ISSUED.\n\nVOLUNTEERS AND MERCENARIES HAVE BEEN STIPULATED AS PROPOSED.\n\nGOOD WORK PEOPLE.\n\nSTAND BY FOR FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS.\n</t>
 <t id="5">[author][green]%s[/green][/author]FLASH %sZ\n\nTO ALL REACHABLE PARTIES\n\nRECON UNITS HAVE IDENTIFIED A TEMPORARY WEAKNESS IN %s OCV DEFENSES.\n\nIMMEDIATE DISPATCH OF RAPID RESPONSE FORCE HAS BEEN ACTIVATED BUT REQUIRES ESCORT FROM VOLUNTEERS.\n\nSTRIKE FORCE IS MEETING IN %s SECTOR CENTER AND WILL JUMP to %s EXACTLY 10 MINUTES FROM THE DELIVERY OF THIS MESSAGE.\n\nVOLUNTEERS AND MERCENARIES WILL STIPULATED AS PROPOSED.\n\nSTAND BY FOR FURTHER INSTRUCTIONS.\n</t>
 <t id="6">[author][green]%s[/green][/author]To private party %s:\n\nIt is with great honour that we present to you this award of %s for assisting in this latest military operation in sector %s. Your efforts have contributed to the eradication of the Omicron Channel Virus.</t>
 <t id="7">[author][green]Galactic Alliance[/green][/author]A new era has begun. Reports from all over the Universe confirm that the threat of the Omicron Channel Virus has been eliminated once and for all. Military mobilization will slowly return to normal levels in the coming weeks, and the lives of the Commonwealth can resume in the relative peaceful existence the Universe once was prior to the horrors exacted upon them by this most insidious and mysterious revelation.</t>
 <t id="8">[author][green]Rebel Aliance[/green][/author]To all reachable parties:\n\nAs you may have already heard through various media channels within your respective homeworlds, it has become apparent that we are not alone in the Omicron Channel sectors. As of yesterday, scout ships in sector %s have reported sightings of what appear to be ships of Xenon and ancient terraformer make assembling within proximity to a Xenon station. While we are unclear of the intentions of this new entity, or if this possible threat is Xenon in nature, we would urge that all scheduled jumps and passage to Vector Prime be restricted.\n\nMore information will be available as New Republic expedition teams continue to uncover the origins and intentions of this new entity.</t>
 <t id="9">OCV Neutralized: \033C%s\033X \033Y%s Cr\033X</t>
 <t id="101">Lando Calrissian</t>
 <t id="102">Admiral Ackbar</t>
 <t id="103">Te Kandosii Mand'alor</t>
 <t id="104">Admiral Trench</t>
 <t id="105">Corporate Sector CEO</t>
 <t id="106">Grand Admiral Thrawn</t>
 <t id="107">The Jedi Council</t>
 <t id="108">Admiral Carth Onasi</t>
 <t id="200">500</t>
 <t id="201">15</t>
 <t id="202">20</t>
 <t id="203">50</t>
 <t id="204">1000</t>
 <t id="205">1000</t>
 <t id="206">2750</t>
 <t id="207">5000</t>
 <t id="208">8000</t>
</page>
<page id="350037" title="Encyclopedia" descr="">
 <t id="10011">The Alliance to Restore the Republic, also known as the Rebel Alliance, was a multitude of rebel groups who sought out the destruction of the Galactic Empire and the re-establishment of the Republic. These rebels were not just one group, but many who fought for their freedom against the tyranny of the Empire.\n\nThe most recognizable group of rebels was lead by former senator Mon Mothma, as well as General Leia Organa, General Han Solo, and more. With the help of now Jedi Luke Skywalker, they successfully lead an attack on the first Death Star, destroying it before it could destroy their base at Yavin 4. After this and a few other victories, the galaxy began to see hope in this new alliance, and many planets either secretly began to support them, or they declared their allegence to them outright.\n\nThe Rebels have never really had a home base or capital, as they adopted a Hit and Run strategy, meaning they were often on the move or being chased down by the Empire. A few of their notable bases or planets were Yavin 4, Hoth, Bothawui, and later Sullust after capturing it from the Empire.</t>
 <t id="10012">The Rebel Alliance relies upon stealing ships from the Empire, or products from planets of which they have captured. Most notably, the Mon Calamari Cruiser series, from Mon Cala shipyards which specialized in heavy shielding and durability. They also utilized many designs from corporations who had secretly been selling them ships. This included Incom Corporation, who had sold them the rebel's most notable starfigther, the T-65 X-Wing. The rebels restored many ships from the clone wars, including the BTL-B A4 Y Wing bomber, and very few sepratist and republic capital ships like Rebel One and the Liberation, which were Providence and Venator class cruisers respectively.\n\nMost rebel ships were either centered around heavy shielding or carrying capacity for the rebellion's many great starfighters, as well as great speed for their hit and run tactics.</t>
 <t id="10021">Secforce refers to groups and peoples who resist the empire. The Secforce groups are not considered a part of the Rebel alliance themselves, as they often operate on different worlds resisting the Empire which would not normally be in reach of the main forces of the Rebel Alliance. Consequently, these forces sometimes use different ships, or havee different morals.</t>
 <t id="10022">Secforces use whatever they can find to fight off the empire, as supplies from the main forces of the Rebel Alliance do not often come through to them. This means that their ships can be very cheap or stolen. However, worlds wealthy enougjh to have legitimate military forces may often use their better ships to defend themselves.</t>
 <t id="10031">The Mandalorians were a group of warriors who were infamous for their battle tactics and fighting styles. They used equipment such as their strong armor made from Mandalorian Iron and Beskar. They also used jetpacks and blaster rifles. Along with their fierce fighting style, they were some of the most feared warriors in the galaxy. During and prior to the Mandalorian Wars, they had many planets that were aligned to them and had a fleet to support them.\nThe Leader of the mandalorians was known as Te Kandossi Mand'alor.</t>
 <t id="10032">Mandalorian ships were usually better the larger and the more modern they got. While most of the time the mandalorians used the Kandosii, they found that it became increasingly outdated compared to the designs of other factions. To supplement the Kandosii, which was also used as a carrier, the mandalorians designed the Keldabe classs battleship, which was strong enough to compete with even the largest of MC80's or ISD's. Dreadnought class heavy cruisers and their own Crusader class corvettes were often used to supplement their heavier ships as well. Their fighter designs were also quite cheap, making them adequate for pirates.</t>
 <t id="10041">The Confederacy of Independent Systems \(CIS\) also known as the Sepratist Aliance, was a confederacy of outer rim planets who separated from the republic due to the mistreatment of worlds in the outer reaches. These planets were often looked down upon by governors and people in the core worlds due to their distance. Finding the confederacy to be a good profit opporotunity, various clans and businesses including the Trade Federation, the Techno Union, and the Intergalactic Banking Clan sought to support the sepratists. The involvment of these corporations gave the sepratists many capital ships and especially a droid army to fight the republic with. \n\nThe sepratists were also supported by Count Dooku, a sith lord who was the pawn of Senator Palpatine who was also manipulating both sides of the war. Having given so much to the sepratists, Dooku and the rest of the corporations who funded them were given control of the droid forces including the Sepratist Navy. Dooku and his close allies formed Dooku's inner circle, the group who had most of the control of the CIS and at some points actually went against the Sepratist Council's motives, which included numerous warcrimes being comitted against the Republic.\n\nThe actual Sepratist Council, located in the Confederacy's capital, Raxus Secundus, had a good cause. They wanted equal rights for people living in the outer rim and their council was far more efficient than the corrupt and bureaucratic mess that was the actual galactic senate. However, this council was not the actual power in the Confederacy, which was actually held in Dooku's Inner Circle. The representatives in the confederacy were only given control of armies that were on their respective homeworlds, and were over all oblivious to the war crimes that Dooku and his Inner CIrcle committed on the battlefield. They instead thought that the Republic was to blame, which in some cases, they actually were.\n\nAfter the end of the clone wars, most droid armies and ships were shut down and abandoned due to Darth Vader sending a shutdown signal from Mustafar. However, not all droids recieved the shutdown signal, and many forces from the cconfederacy remained either in the Unknown Regions, or from the Muun's who were evading the empire in the north. Most sepratist holdouts continued to fight the now reformed Galactic Empire or joined the Rebel Alliance.\n\nAfter Vader was rescued by Palpatine from mustafar, a geonosian called Gizor Dellso restarted a droid factory at Mustafar and was able to build both an army and a navy.</t>
 <t id="10042">The Confederacy relied upon the various corporations that had supported them for ship designs. This included the Munificent class frigate, which was from the Intergalactic Banking clan, originally used as an asset protection unit which was incredibly powerful in formation. Some of their ship designs, such as the Recusant and the Providence, were actually designed and produced by Mon Calamari shiprights that were aligned to the sepratists. Most of the sepratist designs had larger cargo holds that could help them to take control of occupied planets quickly and easily.\n\nUsing their cheap starfighters, the confederacy often relies on swarm tactics.</t>
 <t id="10051">The Republic was a democratic government ruled by a senate and an elected Chancellor. It had been rulling most of the galaxy for thousands of years, until the Clone Wars when Chancellor Palpatine took over the republic and formed the Galactic Empire. \n\nThe Republic spanned many planets from the core, where its capital Coruscant was located to the outer rim. The Republic was often aided by the Jedi Order, a group of force users who favored the light side of the force.\n\nThe Jedi and small republic Judicial forces were the only standing military that the republic had for a long time due to the republic's demilitarization efforts along with the Ruusan reformation. This changed during the start of the clone wars when the republic began a rapid militarization effort under Chancellor Palpatine to combat the Confederacy of Independent Systems.</t>
 <t id="10052">The Republic rely on very few ship designs to do their work. They also do this in accordance to the Ruusan reformation.\n\nMost naval operations by the Republic are led by the Venator Star Destroyer. It is used as a multi role carrier and/or front line battleship \(although it is not classified as a battleship\). Although rarely they use other designs more catered to star destroyers, such as the Legacy Class. Other times they use smaller ships such as the consular, or the arquintens to escort their Venators.\n\nHaving them right at the start of the clone wars, the republic made good use of the Acclamator. The Acclamator was converted to serve as an escort frigate or transport ship depending on the situation. \(Hence its name\)\n\nThe Republic also use more durable and expensive strike craft compared to their CIS counterparts. Instead of a fast and light Vulture droid, the republic settled on a slow, but heavily armed and armored ARC-170. Although the republic also had lighter designs such as the V-19 Torrent or the V-Wing to act in an interceptor role.</t>
 <t id="10081">Pirates are not a race in themselves but groups of like-minded criminals who specialize in all sorts of illegal activities. They have their own bases, usually hidden from view and well defended. Most pirate bases have large fleets of ships and will send out raiding patrols on a regular basis. They are known to be very aggressive and if they spot you across the sector they may start heading your way. \n\nPirates are split into subfactions throughout the galaxy, as their sectors are usually stuck in between those of other races, and clusters of their territory are often separated.\n\nThe Hutts are some of the most known pirates in galactic history. They have always had a major presence in the eastern part of the mid and outer rim territories. They specialize in the spreading of their influence and the running of spice, and because of this they are some of the most wealthy pirates in the galaxy.\n\nThe Zahn Consortium was a crime syndicate run by Tyber Zahn who was an infamous criminal and a wanted individual. His consortium competes with both the Empire and the Rebel Alliance using mandalorian designed ships.\n\nThe Black Sun were very influencial duriing the time of the Clone Wars and the Galactic Civil war. It was lead by Prince Xizor, amongst others. They cooperated with the Zahn consortium at points, as well as assisting the Empire with the construction of the Second Death Star.</t>
 <t id="10091">The Jedi were a group of light side force users. Their principles were based on peace, however this did not stop the Jedi from becoming enforcers and soldiers for the Republic due to their skill in lightsaber combat. The Jedi also had a council that made decisions for the order as a whole, which included some of the most powerful Jedi known.</t>
 <t id="10092">The Jedi were never known to have a fleet, although they used republic designed starships in battles and participated alongside their fellow republic navy. The few ship designs they did use were very light and sometimes lacked some essential systems, as the Jedi could use the force and would not require them. The Jedi would use these really fast and incredibly agile ships to lead a fighter squadron into battle.</t>
 <t id="10181">The Galactic Empire was an empire ruled over by Emperor Palpatine. It rose out of the Republic following the end of the Clone Wars. Palpatine ruled the empire with an iron fist alongside his apprentice Darth Vader.\n\nAfter the war had ended, the Empire went on a campagin to destroy any remaining sepratist holdouts and a rapid militarization of their forces.\n\nThe Empire, as you can tell, was a tyrannical regime that supressed all resistance to the government with brutal force. However, it was not long before major rebellions and resistance movements struck across the galaxy, especially in the outer rim territories. Out of these resistance groups, the Alliance to Restore the Republic was born. In order to quell the rebellion the empire constructed the masssive DS-1 Orbital battlestation, also known as the Death Star. With the death star, the empire destroyed the planet of alderaan, further increasing the resistance to the empire, and the birth of the colony of New Alderaan.\n\nRather unfortunately for the Empire, the Death Star was destroyed over the rebel base at Yavin-4. The destruction of the Death Star lead even more people to join the Aliance.\n\nThe Empire commonly used large ships with as much firepower as they could bear, and following the Tarkin Doctrine, made their ships in order to cement fear into the minds of anyone who had opposed them.\n\nThe most used ships in the empire included the Imperial 1 and Imperial 2 class Star destroyers. Both of them had an impressive amount of turbolasers and ion cannons, being able to rip other ships apart. The Star destroyer class of ships was meant to be fully independent, in the way that it could defeat any defending forces in orbit, and use its large cargobay to assault the surface of a planet and set up a base. It was also capable of performing what the Imperials called, a &quot;Base Delta Zero&quot; when a star destroyer would obliterate anything on the planet using orbital bombardment.\n\nWhile the star destroyers could serve many roles, they were often victim to the Rebels fighter hit and run attacks, as often they were left without escort from smaller ships. This problem was amplified with the Imperial Star Destroyer 2 class, which had not point defense weaponry and its heavier turbolasers had trouble taking down rebel starfighters.\n\nWhen it came to fighters, the Empire relied on light and fast ships to be used in swarm tactics. By using this method, the empire went with the cheap option with most of their fighters, with some of them lacking shields or even a hyperdrive, only relying on its speed and manueverability to survive.</t>
 <t id="10191">The Old Republic was the government people that people refer to when they talk about the Republic that had fought against the Sith Empire. This republic had many of the same principles and shared many similarities with the Republic that fought in the Clone Wars. Its military however, was unhindered by the Ruusan Reformation and was strengthened to combat the Sith.\n\nMost of their ships were smaller that later Republic ships, likely due to a difference in technology and fleet strategy. The Republic most often used the Hammerhead Cruiser, and other models in use closely resembled the hammerhead's design such as the Zenith cruiser.</t>
</page>
</language>
