<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<language id="44">
<page id="17" title="Boardcomp. objects" descr="">
 <t id="4621">Incom Fighter Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="4623">Incom Fighter Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="7933">H9 Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="7934">The H9 Turbolaser Cannon was a model of turbolaser cannon manufacted by Tiam &amp; Bak for use on the CR-90 Corvette. Its relatively light design makes it ideal for destroying fighters. It can also be equipped on other Corvette models and even capital ships. Though it does trade off speed and fire rate, this laser can dismantle fighters much faster than other anti-fighter weaponry.\n\n</t>
 <t id="8001">T&amp;B KX9 Forge</t>
 <t id="8002">This weapons forge manufactures the Tiam &amp; Bak KX9 Laser cannon.</t>
 <t id="8003">T&amp;B KX9 Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8011">T&amp;B KX10 Forge</t>
 <t id="8012">This weapons forge manfactures the Tiam &amp; Bak KX10 Laser cannon</t>
 <t id="8013">T&amp;B KX10 Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8031">B.A.W Mk.2 Laser Forge</t>
 <t id="8033">B.A.W Light Laser Cannon Mk.2</t>
 <t id="8051">B.A.W Mk.1 Laser Forge</t>
 <t id="8053">B.A.W Light Laser Cannon Mk.1</t>
 <t id="8061">IX4-B Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8063">T&amp;B IX4-B Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8071">{17,4621}(Ion Disruptor Forge)</t>
 <t id="8072">{17,4622}(Ion Disruptor Forge description)</t>
 <t id="8073">{17,4623}(Ion Disruptor)</t>
 <t id="8074">{17,4624}(Ion Disruptor description)</t>
 <t id="8081">Mounted Blaster Forge</t>
 <t id="8082">This laser forge manufactures the Mounted Blaster.</t>
 <t id="8083">Mounted Blaster</t>
 <t id="8089">The blaster is simply a modified handheld blaster used on some light spacecraft to harass light ships. It fires very rapidly but does little damage.</t>
 <t id="8091">Pirate Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8092">This production complex manufactures the Pirate Laser Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8093">Pirate Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8099">A light blaster cannon model that is commonly used by pirates to destroy lighter ships.</t>
 <t id="8101">LS-7.2 Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8102">This production facility manufactures the LS-7.2 Laser Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8103">LS-7.2 Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8104">{17,2669} {17,8109}(A weapon mostly found on some medium to larger fighter craft)</t>
 <t id="8109">A heavier and stronger variant of the previous Ls-1 Laser cannon. It is commonly used on heavier imperial fighters and corvettes.</t>
 <t id="8121">A-4 Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8122">This production facility manufactures the A-4 Ion Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8123">A-4 Light Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="8129">A more modern version of the light ion cannon. Does more damage over all and is very efffective at lowering the shields of light to mediium ships. It is slower compared to its older counterpart.</t>
 <t id="8130">A weapon usually found equipped on corvettes or Frigate-sized ships, used for fighter defence.</t>
 <t id="8131">Light Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8132">This production facility manufactures the Light Ion Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8133">Light Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="8139">A smaller and earlier version of the Ion Cannon. It fires considerably faster than the scaled up models but does less damage overal even compared to the newer light ion cannon models.</t>
 <t id="8141">Heavy Blaster Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8142">This production facility manufactures the Heavy Blaster cannon.</t>
 <t id="8143">Heavy Blaster Cannon</t>
 <t id="8151">Flak Artillery Array Forge</t>
 <t id="8153">Flak Artillery Array</t>
 <t id="8159">The Flak Artillery Array is an improved version of the PD Flak cannon that does more damage and fires faster.</t>
 <t id="8161">PD Flak Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8162">This weapons forge produces the Point Defense Flak Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8163">Point Defense Flak Cannon</t>
 <t id="8169">The Point Defense Flak cannon is a fast firing flak cannon that is well suited for missile defense and fighting off small scout ships. It does not do enough damage to be effective at harassing small capital ships or even corvettes.</t>
 <t id="8171">Medium Turbolaser Forge</t>
 <t id="8172">This production facility manufactures the Medium Turbolaser Battery.</t>
 <t id="8173">Medium Turbolaser battery</t>
 <t id="8179">This turbolaser battery is a mix between lighter and heavier variants of the turbolaser. It can fire very fast with decent range. It can be used against fighters but not very effectively.</t>
 <t id="8181">CIS Heavy Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8183">CIS Heavy Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8184">The CIS heavy laser cannon was a laser cannon designed by the CIS to counter fighters and corvettes.</t>
 <t id="8191">Imperial Flak Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8192">This production facility manufactures the Imperial Flak Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8193">Imperial Flak Cannon</t>
 <t id="8199">The Imperial Flak Cannon was a flak cannon designed for use in the Galactic Empire against missiles and rarely for fighter defense. it fires very fast but does llittle damage.</t>
 <t id="8201">Heavy Turbolaser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8202">This production complex produces the Heavy Turbolaser.</t>
 <t id="8203">Heavy Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8204">The Heavy Turbolaser Cannon was one of the heaviest and strongest turbolasers ever made. It is only used by larger capital ships, has better range and damage than other designs but fires very, very slowly.</t>
 <t id="8211">Heavy Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8212">This weapons forge produces the Ion Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8213">Heavy Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="8219">The Ion cannon is most ship captian's answers for going against ships with strong shields. These cannons do very heavy damage to shields but fires very slowly.</t>
 <t id="8221">Gauss Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8222">This production facility manufactures the Gauss Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8223">Gauss Cannon</t>
 <t id="8229">An upscaled mass driver cannon designed as a kinetic competitor to turbolasers.</t>
 <t id="8231">Pirate Heavy Turbolaser Battery Forge</t>
 <t id="8232">This weapons forge manufactures the Pirate Heavy Turbolaser Battery.</t>
 <t id="8233">Pirate Heavy Turbolaser Battery</t>
 <t id="8239">Unable to easily gain possession of high-tech capital ship weapons, pirates designed this as an alternative. The Pirate heavy turbolaser is a pirate modification to the heavy turbolaser batteries.</t>
 <t id="8241">XX-9 Heavy Turbolaser Forge</t>
 <t id="8242">This production facility manufactures the XX-9 Heavy Turbolaser.</t>
 <t id="8243">XX-9 Heavy Turbolaser</t>
 <t id="8249">The XX-9 Heavy Turbolaser was a revision of previous heavy turbolaser models that further traded mobility and fire rate for damage.</t>
 <t id="8261">Sepratist Turbolaser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8262">This weapons forge manufactures the Sepratist Turbolaser Cannon.</t>
 <t id="8263">Separatist Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="8269">Needing an alternative for Republic turbolaser designs, the separatists designed the their own turbolaser cannon for mass production.</t>
 <t id="8271">Medium Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="8272">This weapons forge manufactures the Medium Ion Cannon.\n</t>
 <t id="8273">Medium Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="8279">Medium Ion cannon that fires relatively fast that can be found on most ships.</t>
 <t id="9503">XV9 Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="9505">Sienar Fighter Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="9507">LS-7 Light Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="9511">XV9 Turbolaser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="9513">Sienar Fighter Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="9515">LS-7 Light Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="9516">This weapons forge manufactures the LS-7 Light Laser cannon.</t>
 <t id="99800">CIS Siege Battery</t>
 <t id="99965">Rebel Siege Turbolaser</t>
 <t id="99970">Imperial Octuple Turbolaser</t>
 <t id="99992">CIS Siege Battery Forge</t>
</page>
</language>
