<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<language id="44">
<page id="7" title="Boardcomp. Sectornames" descr="Names of all sectors (spoken by Boardcomputer)">
 <t id="1020101">Firefist Epsilon</t>
 <t id="1020102">Firefist Delta</t>
 <t id="1020103">Firefist Zeta</t>
 <t id="1020104">Firefist Eta</t>
 <t id="1020105">Firefist Theta</t>
 <t id="1020106">Firefist Iota</t>
 <t id="1020110">Mortis</t>
 <t id="1020112">Belkadan</t>
 <t id="1020118">Unknown Sector Omega</t>
 <t id="1020119">Saffalore</t>
 <t id="1020120">Bonadan</t>
 <t id="1020201">Firefist Alpha</t>
 <t id="1020202">Firefist Beta</t>
 <t id="1020203">Firefist Gamma</t>
 <t id="1020204">Firefist Omega</t>
 <t id="1020205">Firefist Kappa</t>
 <t id="1020209">Entralla</t>
 <t id="1020210">Kalee</t>
 <t id="1020211">Dubrillion</t>
 <t id="1020212">Helska</t>
 <t id="1020213">Sernidipal</t>
 <t id="1020214">Birgis</t>
 <t id="1020215">Tangrene</t>
 <t id="1020216">Serenno</t>
 <t id="1020217">Telos</t>
 <t id="1020218">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020219">Paragus Asteroids</t>
 <t id="1020220">Reltooine</t>
 <t id="1020221">Etti IV</t>
 <t id="1020224">Ession</t>
 <t id="1020305">The Redoubt</t>
 <t id="1020309">Yaga Minor</t>
 <t id="1020310">Jaemus</t>
 <t id="1020311">Bastion</t>
 <t id="1020312">Dantooine</t>
 <t id="1020313">Dantooine</t>
 <t id="1020314">Akuria II</t>
 <t id="1020315">Dathomir</t>
 <t id="1020316">Nez Peron</t>
 <t id="1020317">Yavin IV</t>
 <t id="1020318">Arda</t>
 <t id="1020319">Korriban</t>
 <t id="1020321">Malachor</t>
 <t id="1020323">Raxus Secundus</t>
 <t id="1020324">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020405">Ugeetu Nebula</t>
 <t id="1020406">Illum</t>
 <t id="1020409">Adumar</t>
 <t id="1020410">Aeten II</t>
 <t id="1020411">Muunilist</t>
 <t id="1020412">Mygeeto</t>
 <t id="1020413">Ithor</t>
 <t id="1020414">Agamar</t>
 <t id="1020415">Taris</t>
 <t id="1020416">Scipio</t>
 <t id="1020417">Botajef</t>
 <t id="1020418">Anteevy</t>
 <t id="1020419">Vanquo</t>
 <t id="1020423">Raxus Prime</t>
 <t id="1020424">Pammant</t>
 <t id="1020503">Unknown Sector Alpha</t>
 <t id="1020504">Copero</t>
 <t id="1020505">Csilla</t>
 <t id="1020507">Copero</t>
 <t id="1020508">Csilla</t>
 <t id="1020509">Ansion</t>
 <t id="1020510">Orinda</t>
 <t id="1020511">Iridonia</t>
 <t id="1020512">Ord Mantell</t>
 <t id="1020513">Corsin</t>
 <t id="1020514">Ralltir</t>
 <t id="1020515">Aquaris</t>
 <t id="1020516">Wayland</t>
 <t id="1020517">Mandalore</t>
 <t id="1020518">Concord Dawn</t>
 <t id="1020519">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020520">Ringo Vinda</t>
 <t id="1020523">Pakuuni</t>
 <t id="1020524">Mon Cala</t>
 <t id="1020604">Xenon Sector 239</t>
 <t id="1020605">Unknown Sector Theta</t>
 <t id="1020610">Bilbringi</t>
 <t id="1020611">Borleias</t>
 <t id="1020613">Brentaal IV</t>
 <t id="1020614">Castell</t>
 <t id="1020615">Carida</t>
 <t id="1020616">Myrkr</t>
 <t id="1020617">Tanaab</t>
 <t id="1020618">Hapes</t>
 <t id="1020619">Trandosha</t>
 <t id="1020620">Boz Pity</t>
 <t id="1020621">Saleucemi</t>
 <t id="1020622">Jabim</t>
 <t id="1020623">Lothal</t>
 <t id="1020624">New Alderaan</t>
 <t id="1020704">Xenon Sector 199</t>
 <t id="1020705">Rakkata Prime</t>
 <t id="1020707">Unknown Sector Zeta</t>
 <t id="1020708">Jedha</t>
 <t id="1020710">Fresia</t>
 <t id="1020711">Coruscant</t>
 <t id="1020712">Anaxes</t>
 <t id="1020713">Corulag</t>
 <t id="1020714">Neimodia</t>
 <t id="1020715">Skako</t>
 <t id="1020716">Alderaan</t>
 <t id="1020717">Onderon</t>
 <t id="1020718">Umbara</t>
 <t id="1020719">Kashyyk</t>
 <t id="1020720">Roche Asteroids</t>
 <t id="1020721">Klatooine</t>
 <t id="1020722">Kessel</t>
 <t id="1020723">The Maw</t>
 <t id="1020724">Oba Diah</t>
 <t id="1020803">Xenon Core 086</t>
 <t id="1020804">Xenon Sector 584</t>
 <t id="1020805">Xenon Core 075</t>
 <t id="1020807">Unknown Sector Rho</t>
 <t id="1020808">Unknown Sector Gamma</t>
 <t id="1020810">Galantos</t>
 <t id="1020811">Foerost</t>
 <t id="1020812">Aargau</t>
 <t id="1020813">Chandrilla</t>
 <t id="1020814">Kuat</t>
 <t id="1020815">Balmorra</t>
 <t id="1020816">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020817">Commenor</t>
 <t id="1020818">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020820">Nimban</t>
 <t id="1020821">Saki</t>
 <t id="1020822">Honoghr</t>
 <t id="1020824">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1020904">Xenon Sector 187</t>
 <t id="1020909">Unknown Sector Lambda</t>
 <t id="1020910">Sanctuary of Darkness</t>
 <t id="1020911">Byss</t>
 <t id="1020912">Empress Teta</t>
 <t id="1020914">Rendilli</t>
 <t id="1020915">Corellia</t>
 <t id="1020916">Skako</t>
 <t id="1020917">Manaan</t>
 <t id="1020918">Belasco</t>
 <t id="1020919">Ruusan</t>
 <t id="1020920">Toydaria</t>
 <t id="1020921">Da Soocha IV</t>
 <t id="1020922">Eadu</t>
 <t id="1020923">Teth</t>
 <t id="1020924">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021002">Unknown Sepratist Holdout</t>
 <t id="1021003">Xenon Core 009</t>
 <t id="1021004">Xenon Sector 332</t>
 <t id="1021006">Xenon Sector 706</t>
 <t id="1021012">Unknown Sector Beta</t>
 <t id="1021013">Sarapin</t>
 <t id="1021014">Abregado Rae</t>
 <t id="1021015">Duro</t>
 <t id="1021016">Exodeen</t>
 <t id="1021017">Mimban</t>
 <t id="1021018">Attahox</t>
 <t id="1021019">Quesh</t>
 <t id="1021020">Nal Hutta</t>
 <t id="1021021">Ylesia</t>
 <t id="1021022">Shola</t>
 <t id="1021024">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021102">Unknown Sector Iota</t>
 <t id="1021105">Unknown Sector Iota</t>
 <t id="1021106">Xenon Sector 521</t>
 <t id="1021107">Wild Space Sector</t>
 <t id="1021110">Jakku</t>
 <t id="1021112">Tython</t>
 <t id="1021113">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021114">Ghorman</t>
 <t id="1021115">Fondor</t>
 <t id="1021116">Denon</t>
 <t id="1021117">Ghorman</t>
 <t id="1021118">Pasaana</t>
 <t id="1021119">Dressel</t>
 <t id="1021121">Gamorr</t>
 <t id="1021124">Gamorr</t>
 <t id="1021201">Intergalactic Void</t>
 <t id="1021202">Lwhekk</t>
 <t id="1021204">Intergalactic Void</t>
 <t id="1021205">Lwhekk</t>
 <t id="1021206">Unknown Sector Delta</t>
 <t id="1021210">Batuu</t>
 <t id="1021212">Ring of Kafrene</t>
 <t id="1021213">Batuu</t>
 <t id="1021214">Thyferra</t>
 <t id="1021215">Bestine</t>
 <t id="1021216">Azterri</t>
 <t id="1021217">Aridus</t>
 <t id="1021218">Nexus Ortal</t>
 <t id="1021219">Bothawui</t>
 <t id="1021220">Kothlis</t>
 <t id="1021221">Lyran IV</t>
 <t id="1021222">Wild Space Sector</t>
 <t id="1021303">Unknown Enemy Sector Beta</t>
 <t id="1021304">Zakuul</t>
 <t id="1021305">Unknown Enemy Sector Alpha</t>
 <t id="1021306">Unknown Sector Epsilon</t>
 <t id="1021307">Old Republic Holdout</t>
 <t id="1021308">Xenon Sector 671</t>
 <t id="1021309">Xenon Core 067</t>
 <t id="1021314">Mechis III</t>
 <t id="1021316">Kooriva</t>
 <t id="1021317">Zolan</t>
 <t id="1021318">Falleen</t>
 <t id="1021319">Rishi Moon</t>
 <t id="1021320">Ukio</t>
 <t id="1021321">Scarrif</t>
 <t id="1021322">Rothana</t>
 <t id="1021401">Brentaal Moon Base</t>
 <t id="1021406">Ach-To</t>
 <t id="1021407">Unknown Sector Omicron</t>
 <t id="1021408">Unknown Sector Chi</t>
 <t id="1021409">Unknown Sector Eta</t>
 <t id="1021410">Rattatak</t>
 <t id="1021413">Ord Ibanna</t>
 <t id="1021414">Wroona</t>
 <t id="1021416">Rintonne</t>
 <t id="1021417">Tatooine</t>
 <t id="1021418">Geonosis</t>
 <t id="1021419">Roon</t>
 <t id="1021420">Kamino</t>
 <t id="1021421">Geonosis</t>
 <t id="1021422">Roon</t>
 <t id="1021423">Kamino</t>
 <t id="1021424">Rishi Maze</t>
 <t id="1021425">Fucking Hell</t>
 <t id="1021501">Debug and Testing</t>
 <t id="1021508">Xenon Sector 442</t>
 <t id="1021509">Bakura</t>
 <t id="1021510">Moddel Systems</t>
 <t id="1021511">Cerea</t>
 <t id="1021512">Kriselist</t>
 <t id="1021513">Qat Chrystac</t>
 <t id="1021514">Malastare</t>
 <t id="1021515">Naboo</t>
 <t id="1021516">Zhar</t>
 <t id="1021517">Christophsis</t>
 <t id="1021518">Rodia</t>
 <t id="1021519">Hypori</t>
 <t id="1021520">Excarga</t>
 <t id="1021521">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021522">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021523">MISSING</t>
 <t id="1021601">Uncharted Space</t>
 <t id="1021602">Helska</t>
 <t id="1021603">Anoth</t>
 <t id="1021604">Haven</t>
 <t id="1021608">Sluis Van</t>
 <t id="1021610">Endor</t>
 <t id="1021611">Unknown Sector Pi</t>
 <t id="1021612">Bespin</t>
 <t id="1021613">Alluyen</t>
 <t id="1021614">Sullust</t>
 <t id="1021615">Crait</t>
 <t id="1021616">D'Qar</t>
 <t id="1021617">Socorro</t>
 <t id="1021618">Ryloth</t>
 <t id="1021619">Siskeen</t>
 <t id="1021701">Grek Gamma</t>
 <t id="1021702">Grek Beta</t>
 <t id="1021703">Grek Alpha</t>
 <t id="1021704">Grek Delta</t>
 <t id="1021705">Grek Beta</t>
 <t id="1021706">Grek Alpha</t>
 <t id="1021708">Polis Massa</t>
 <t id="1021711">Virgillia VII</t>
 <t id="1021712">Anoat</t>
 <t id="1021713">Senex-Juvex Systems</t>
 <t id="1021714">Eraidu</t>
 <t id="1021715">Xagobah</t>
 <t id="1021716">Golrath</t>
 <t id="1021717">Vergesso Asteroids</t>
 <t id="1021718">Naos III</t>
 <t id="1021719">Golrath</t>
 <t id="1021720">Vergesso Asteroids</t>
 <t id="1021721">Naos III</t>
 <t id="1021810">Dosuun</t>
 <t id="1021811">Thakwaa</t>
 <t id="1021812">Hoth</t>
 <t id="1021813">Tureen VII</t>
 <t id="1021814">Triton</t>
 <t id="1021815">Utapau</t>
 <t id="1021816">Sluis Van</t>
 <t id="1021817">Alzoc III</t>
 <t id="1021902">Friendlies</t>
 <t id="1021903">Attackers</t>
 <t id="1021910">Seoul</t>
 <t id="1021912">Anoth</t>
 <t id="1021913">Mustafar</t>
 <t id="1021914">Dagobah</t>
 <t id="1021915">Polis Massa</t>
 <t id="1021923">Rishi Maze</t>
 <t id="1022010">Red Nebula</t>
 <t id="1022012">Haven</t>
 <t id="1022015">Terminus</t>
 <t id="1023824">Oba Diah</t>
 <t id="1023832">Unclaimed Sector</t>
</page>
<page id="17" title="" descr="">
 <t id="5093">Rebel One</t>
</page>
<page id="19" title="Boardcomp. Descriptions" descr="">
 <t id="1030210">Kalee is a tropical planet home to the Kaleesh species, a notable Kaleesh being General Grievous. The planet itself has historically been embroiled in constant conflict, causing mass poverty. The warfare would come in handy however, with the Kaleesh being able to fend of the Empire.</t>
 <t id="1030316">Although the fledgling farming collective of Nez Peron actively resists Imperial control, the Empire has sought to locking the sector down as it remains a key staging point for assaulting the Rebel Alliance.</t>
 <t id="1030504">Copero is a planet of the Chiss Ascendancy jointly defended by the Chiss Expeditionary Defense Force and the Imperial Navy in the Unknown Regions. It sits on key hyperlane routes in and outside of Chiss Space in addition to being home to the largest of the Chiss shipyards. Thus, it is heavily defended.\n\nContains: Chiss Expeditionary Defense Shipyards\n</t>
 <t id="1030505">Csilla is the home of the Chiss Species, it is also a frozen hellscape.\nThe Chiss are known to be cooperative with the Empire, aiding in exploration efforts of the unknown regions and contributing naval intelligence. This sector and subsequent area of space is heavily guarded, and only supplies and military forces are allowed to travel this deep into space.</t>
 <t id="1030508">This sector was discovered in intial expeditions into the Unknown region by the Chiss and the Empire. The sector would be the site of a small scale mining operation until the Imperial and Chiss forces were forced to retreat in the threat of being encircled by Xenon forces. Other than the large debris field, this sector is featureless besides the occasional xenon patrol.</t>
 <t id="1030512">Ord Mantell has long been a center of commerce and strategic importance, as well as crime. This sytem is now in a state of continuous conflict between the Rebel Alliance and imperial occupational forces. Meanwhile, neutral traders and subsequent pirates profit off of the conflict, delivering and intercepting goods to and from both sides.</t>
 <t id="1030520">Ringo Vinda is a shipbuilding and manufacturing world currently occupied by remaining forces of the Confederacy of Independent Systems in dire straits under siege from the Empire.</t>
 <t id="1030605">This sector was originally the site of settlements by the Chiss, who had used it as a recon outpost. This was until the Xenon had arrived at the edge of the unknown regions, presumably via intergalactic transportation methods unknown to the rest of galactic civilzation. The newly arrived Xenon, who had brought with them a substantial military force, overwhelmed the defenses of the sector, causing a mass retreat of Imperial and Chiss forces to Copero. Since then, this sector has been fortified and is used as a staging point to conduct attacks against the Empire.</t>
 <t id="1030608">Rakkata Prime, or Lehon as it is known by its former population is a cold and barren system full of ruins from the now fallen Infinite Empire. Although once a heavily regulated tourist site, it remains out of the way and unaccessable by normal travelers due to recent shifts in hyperlanes in the unknown region. As of recent, a sign of life was detected on the outskirts of the system. Whether it was simply a xenon passing by or a theorized reborn rakkatan is unknown.</t>
 <t id="1030710">Fresia is an ocean-blue core world known for being the headquarters of the Incom Corporation. Incom ships can be purchased here, yet they are rarely used by the Galactic Empire, and blueprints and service-ready products are commonly lost to &quot;smuggling&quot;. Whatever that means.\n\nContains: Incom Corporation Shipyards</t>
 <t id="1030719">Kashyyk is a Mid Rim planet and the lush, wroshyr tree-filled homeworld of the Wookiees. It was a member of the Galactic Republic and was enslaved under the Galactic Empire before being liberated by and subsequently becoming a key ally to the Rebel Alliance. The Wookies bravely defended their homes from the Trandoshans and the Sepratists, and now aim to restore the Republic that once came to their rescue leading up to Order 66.\n\nContains: Alliance Republic Navy Restoration Shipyards</t>
 <t id="1030804">This sector lies at an intersection between xenon space. It is often infested by xenon traffic, although not much else is known.</t>
 <t id="1030811">Foerost was once the site of a Republic Navy black-site that housed a significant shipyard. The ships built would be ferried to Corsucant for deployments in the Inner Rim and Expansion Territories. The planet had little else to its name though, and after being used by General Grievous to launch his attack on Coruscant, the shipyard facilities were abandoned. No longer needing to be kept hidden, the now Imperial shipbuilding capacity would be moved elsewhere, leaving the system devoid of any investment since.</t>
 <t id="1030814">Kuat is a planet located in the Core Worlds and was one of the earliest members of the Galactic Republic. It is best known for the circular shipyards that stretch around the planet, serving as the primary construction and design facilities for both the Republic and the Empire. The planet is primarily inhabited by the Kuati, a subset of humans who lived in a matriarchal society reknowned for their shipbuilding abilities.\n\nContains: Kuat Driveyards, Empire Commercial Engineering</t>
 <t id="1030910">This sector and the local planet of N`Zoth have been leased to the Phanon Corporation by the Galactic Empire. In exchange for handling the costs of garrisoning the system and generating economic output for the Empire, the Phanon Corporation is given free reign in this sector.</t>
 <t id="1030917">Manaan is a beautiful ocean world, with a comparably rebellious populace. This sytem is isolated from most Rebel Alliance activities, but stays free under thin supply lines and shady business. \n\nThe Rebel Alliance has sought out the security of this sector at all costs with the loss of the system marking the loss of control of supply lines near Hutt Space as well as a key front in assaulting the Core Worlds.\n\nContains: Independent Shipyards</t>
 <t id="1030918">The Belasco system is considered to be one of the most guarded Imperial border systems due to its strategic importance to the Empire. Losing this sector would mean losing its grip on Hutt Space, and the cutting off of Imperial supply lines to the Maw and Kessel.</t>
 <t id="1030919">Ruusan is a planet in the Mid Rim most famous for the Ruusan campaign, the last stand of the Brotherhood of Darkness under Lord Kaan and the birthplace of Darth Bane's Order of the Sith Lords. The planet lent its name to the Ruusan Reformations enacted after the battle. Nowadays it is the site of considerable Rebel Alliance activity as the sector was largely forgotten about after the Clone Wars by the Empire.\n\nContains: Alliance Underground Engineering Shipyards</t>
 <t id="1031002">Scattered after the rise of the Galactic Empire, this sector holds a considerable amount of forces belonging to the Confederacy of Independent Systems. The forces that remained after the hyperspace accident during the retreat away from the galaxy set up stations and colonized the nearby moon. Along with the sad fate of this sector's population, it is under constant attack by the Xenon.</t>
 <t id="1031013">Sarapin is the center of a significant amount of the Core World's electricity production. In addition to extreme heat from the sun that provides solar energy, the planet itself hosts plenty of geothermal activity.</t>
 <t id="1031102">This barren sector remains as a grim reminder of the dire straits faced by the remnants of the Sepratists trapped in the unknown regions. It was once a hotbed for mining by the desperate sepratists, who hoped to use the resources to bolster defenses and attempt a breakout, but before any semblence of a breakout came the debris fields which had supplied the sepratist flotilla had been entirely depleted, and thus the already thinly stretched forces of the confederacy had to abandon the sector.</t>
 <t id="1031200">This sector is located outside of the boundary of the galaxy, only being reachable via special hyperlane routes. This sector recieves little to no light, the only light source that it does recieve is that of galaxies in the distance, and this sector is rendered featureless besides a few pieces of debris due to its position.</t>
 <t id="1031307">Amongst the many chaotic reaches of the unknown region lie the remnants of what seem to be scattered forces of the Old Republic trapped in time. This sector is constantly under seige by the neighboring xenon and some other unknown force.</t>
 <t id="1031317">Zolan was a world much like Mon Cala, in that its sentient inhabitants were divided into two, the Zolanders and Clawdites. Clawdites were the result of experimentation on Zolanders that had fallen ill to a meteorite-borne skin contagion.\n \nA notable clawdite, Zam Wessel, had attempted to assasinate Padmé Amidala during the Sepratist Crisis. After the clone wars, The Empire blockaded the planet, restricting it from interacting with the rest of the galaxy. \n\nThough the blockade ended, neither the Empire no Rebel Alliance had any ventures in influencing or conquering the planet.</t>
 <t id="1031509">Bakura is a rich, green and blue planet in the Bakura system of the Shiritoku Spur, located on the isolated edge of Wild Space and near the Unknown Region that was colonized by humans now known as Bakurans. Bakura had a heavy repulsorlift manufacturing industry, despite the planet being devoid of a significant amount of droids due to tariffs that would have otherwise aided assembly line production.\n\nAlthough initially accepting of Imperial occupation \(with the help of several purges\) a battle in Bakuran space occurred between the Alliance to Restore the Republic and the Galactic Empire as part of the Galactic Civil War. With the help of Blue Squadron, the Alliance was victorious in space and the Rebel Alliance was able to swiftly take the planet making heavy use of combined arms tactics and air support.\n\nContains: Bakuran Shipyards, Rebel Underground Engineering Shipyards</t>
 <t id="1031510">This sector exists as an abstraction of numerous systems and habitable planets. Located in the Outer Rim Territories near to Bakura and Endor, the Moddel Systems comprise of an Imperial black site, but despite this the Rebel Alliance has established multiple sympathetic governments in this sector's worlds making use of several corrupt Imperial officials stationed in the area. The Rebels make also consistent use of the hyperlanes within the sector for ferrying supplies, fleets, and Bakuran engineering genius to the wider galaxy.</t>
 <t id="1031520">The mining world of Excarga was once inhabited by forces of the Confederacy of Independent systems before the Darth Vader had wiped most of the sepratist leaders out at Mustafar. Although it is still visited by Imperial mining expeditions, the system lays abandoned.</t>
 <t id="1031616">Socorro is an arid planet tucked far away from galactic activities, with no unifying force present on the planet. The only kind of administrations or governments present are tribes and organized crime.</t>
 <t id="1031712">Anoat is one of three habitable planets in the Anoat system of the Anoat sector, located in the Greater Javin of the Outer Rim. It is located between the Hoth system and the Bespin system. Its primary inhabited settlement is Anoat City, and the planet is home to a Rebel Alliance manufacturing base and several supply depots serving as a key logistical outpost for the few conventional warfare operations of the Rebel Alliance.</t>
 <t id="1031713">This sector exists as an abstraction of numerous systems and habitable planets. The Senex-Juvex systems have existed largely independent from major powers in galactic history, and thus continue to remain independent from the Galactic Civil War. This does come at a cost however, as the wealthy worlds of the sector pay considerable tribute to both sides in the form of hard credits to the Empire and engineering and agricultural assistance to the Rebel Alliance. Thus, they remain outside of the conflict, but not necessarily away from it.</t>
 <t id="1031717">The Vergesso asteroid field \(not to be confused with the asteroid Vergesso\) is an incredibly dense asteroid field located in the Lybeya system. It is home to an Imperial supply depot and limited mining operations. The Rebel Alliance also retains an asteroid base in the sector.</t>
 <t id="1031718">Naos III is a moon located in the Naos system with one habitable area on the entire moon. Many colonists from Ryloth and Rodia were lured to the moon in hopes of finding spice in the moon's volcanic areas. Other than the Naos Mercantile, who currently operates the deteriorating infrastructure on the moon, no outside influence has reached the moon.\n\nA point of particular interest noted by Wookiepedia, Naos III contained a large amount of female Lethan Twi'leks.</t>
 <t id="1031817">Alzoc III was a rarely visited world in the days of the Republic, with the only sentient species on the frigid surface being the native Talz. This was all until the Empire came along, who promptly enslaved the population to exploit the resources of the planet and the surrounding debris fields.</t>
 <t id="1031913">Mustafar is a molten world situated in the Outer Rim Territories. After the destruction of the Separatist Council and the Imperialization of the Techno Union, Mustafar was largely forgotten, until a Separatist stalwart, the fugitive Geonosian Gizor Dellso, holed up on Mustafar during the early days of the Galactic Empire and re-activated an independent battle droid factory, intending to rebuild the Confederacy's previous military strength.\n\nContains: Independent Shipyard, Hoersch-Kessel Drive Branch Shipyards</t>
</page>
<page id="1266" title="Racenames" descr="Strings for the races">
 <t id="1">Rebel Alliance</t>
 <t id="2">Rebel Secforce</t>
 <t id="3">Mandalorian</t>
 <t id="4">Separatist Holdouts</t>
 <t id="5">Corporate Sector</t>
 <t id="6">Xenon</t>
 <t id="7">Khillik</t>
 <t id="8">Pirates</t>
 <t id="9">Jedi</t>
 <t id="11">Enemy Race</t>
 <t id="12">Neutral Race</t>
 <t id="13">Friendly Race</t>
 <t id="14">Unknown</t>
 <t id="15">Race 1</t>
 <t id="16">Race 2</t>
 <t id="17">Remnant</t>
 <t id="18">Race 4</t>
 <t id="19">Race 5</t>
</page>
<page id="1907" title="Stock Exchange Text" descr="">
 <t id="21">\033G%s\033X</t>
 <t id="22">\033R%s\033X</t>
 <t id="23">\033Y%s\033X</t>
 <t id="24">\033C%s\033X</t>
 <t id="25">\033B%s\033X</t>
 <t id="26">\033O%s\033X</t>
 <t id="30">\033Y%s:\033X</t>
 <t id="50">\033G\053\033X</t>
 <t id="51">\033R-\033X</t>
 <t id="52">Yes</t>
 <t id="53">No</t>
 <t id="54">\033G^\033X</t>
 <t id="55">\033Rv\033X</t>
 <t id="56">Show \033GAll\033X:</t>
 <t id="57">Hide \033GAll\033X:</t>
 <t id="58">\033R^\033X</t>
 <t id="59">\033Gv\033X</t>
 <t id="60">G</t>
 <t id="61">R</t>
 <t id="62">Y</t>
 <t id="63">C</t>
 <t id="64">B</t>
 <t id="65">O</t>
 <t id="66">M</t>
 <t id="67">A</t>
 <t id="68">W</t>
 <t id="69">K</t>
 <t id="81">%s</t>
 <t id="82">%s%s</t>
 <t id="83">%s%s%s</t>
 <t id="92">%s %s</t>
 <t id="95">%s - %s</t>
 <t id="100">st.ex.%s.%s</t>
 <t id="301">\033CStock Exchange\033X</t>
 <t id="302">View Local Stock Exchanges</t>
 <t id="303">Stock Exchange Interface</t>
 <t id="306">Corporate / Company Indexes</t>
 <t id="307">View Corporate / Company Indexes</t>
 <t id="308">Commodities</t>
 <t id="309">View Commodities Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="310">View Corporate Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="311">View Company Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="312">Broker Settings</t>
 <t id="316">Stock Exchange</t>
 <t id="601">\033CLocal Exchange for \033C</t>
 <t id="602">\033G%s \033CExchanges:\033X</t>
 <t id="603">Local Stock Exchanges</t>
 <t id="609">Detailed Summary of Shares Owned</t>
 <t id="611">\033GShow\033X</t>
 <t id="612">\033RHide\033X</t>
 <t id="613">Show / Hide:</t>
 <t id="616">No Stock Exchange Found</t>
 <t id="701">\033CExchange:\033X</t>
 <t id="702">%s [ %s ] %s</t>
 <t id="703">\033CLocal Products:\033X</t>
 <t id="704">\033CStock:\033X</t>
 <t id="705">\033CRequired:\033X</t>
 <t id="706">\033CMin Cr:\033X</t>
 <t id="707">\033CMax Cr:\033X</t>
 <t id="708">\033CTrading At:\033X</t>
 <t id="709">\033CIndex:\033X</t>
 <t id="710">\033COwned Shares:\033X</t>
 <t id="711">\033CBought At:\033X</t>
 <t id="712">\033CTotal Paid:\033X</t>
 <t id="713">\033CValue:\033X</t>
 <t id="714">-- None --</t>
 <t id="715">--</t>
 <t id="716">%s Cr</t>
 <t id="718">%s: %s Cr</t>
 <t id="719">Local Stock Exchange</t>
 <t id="720">\033CTotals:\033X</t>
 <t id="722">\033YGrand Totals:\033X</t>
 <t id="724">Show Minimum:</t>
 <t id="725">Show Maximum:</t>
 <t id="726">Cr</t>
 <t id="727">Player Credits:</t>
 <t id="728">%s ***</t>
 <t id="729">\033CSupply:\033X</t>
 <t id="730">\033CDemand:\033X</t>
 <t id="731">\033CAvail Shares:\033X</t>
 <t id="732">\033CNet Profit:\033X</t>
 <t id="733">Total Net Profit / Loss on Owned Shares:</t>
 <t id="734">\033CShares Value:\033X</t>
 <t id="735">\033RPaid\033X \033C/\033X \033GReceived\033X\033C:\033X</t>
 <t id="736">\033CTotal Invested:\033X</t>
 <t id="737">\033YGrand Total Invested:\033X</t>
 <t id="801">\033CCurrent Share Details for:\033X</t>
 <t id="802">Current Shares Owned</t>
 <t id="803">\033CBuy Shares:\033X</t>
 <t id="804">\033GBuy\033X Shares:</t>
 <t id="805">\033CSell Shares:\033X</t>
 <t id="806">\033GSell\033X Shares:</t>
 <t id="807">Current Credits per Share:</t>
 <t id="808">Shares Bought at - Avg Cr:</t>
 <t id="809">Total Credits paid for current Shares:</t>
 <t id="810">Total Value of Owned Shares at Current Price:</t>
 <t id="813">Return to Previous Menu:</t>
 <t id="814">Buy / Sell Shares:</t>
 <t id="816">%s Shares will cost you %s Cr. Proceed Yes / No ?</t>
 <t id="818">%s Credits will be deposited into your Account. Proceed Yes / No ?</t>
 <t id="820">Using Credits:</t>
 <t id="821">Commands:</t>
 <t id="822">ERROR!</t>
 <t id="825">Approx Republic Brokerage fee per share at %s%</t>
 <t id="826">Current Shares Available:</t>
 <t id="827">Less than 1</t>
 <t id="828">You don't have enough credits to buy any shares</t>
 <t id="829">No shares are available at this time</t>
 <t id="901">Corporation and Company Indexes</t>
 <t id="904">\033CCorporation Name:\033X</t>
 <t id="905">\033CCompany Name:\033X</t>
 <t id="906">\033RBuying\033X</t>
 <t id="907">\033GSelling\033X</t>
 <t id="908">Currently Viewing Index from %s Perspective: At \033CIndex\033X \033G100\033X being the best time for %s - \033CSelect to Change:\033X</t>
 <t id="909">Menu View Options:</t>
 <t id="911">Select to Show \033YOwned\033X Shares Only:</t>
 <t id="912">Select to Show \033YAll\033X Shares:</t>
 <t id="913">%s %s \033Yfrom\033X %s \033Yto\033X %s:</t>
 <t id="914">Corporation Index</t>
 <t id="915">Company Index</t>
 <t id="1201">Commodities Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="1202">\033CSorting:\033X</t>
 <t id="1203">Sort by Timeline:</t>
 <t id="1204">Sort by Exchange:</t>
 <t id="1205">Sort by Bought / Sold:</t>
 <t id="1206">Sort by Ware Type:</t>
 <t id="1207">Bought</t>
 <t id="1208">Sold</t>
 <t id="1209">\033CReport:\033X</t>
 <t id="1210">\033CAction:\033X</t>
 <t id="1211">\033CPlaying Time:\033X</t>
 <t id="1212">\033CExchange:\033X</t>
 <t id="1213">\033CWare:\033X</t>
 <t id="1214">\033CCr / Share:\033X</t>
 <t id="1215">\033CGross Credits:\033X</t>
 <t id="1216">\033CNet Credits:\033X</t>
 <t id="1217">\033CFees:\033X</t>
 <t id="1218">\033CAmount:\033X</t>
 <t id="1219">\033CShares:\033X</t>
 <t id="1220">Print to Log File [ %s%s ] HD:\\My Documents\\Egosoft\\X3AP\\log0%s.txt</t>
 <t id="1221">\033RDelete\033X Transaction Records: %s</t>
 <t id="1222">Are you sure you want to \033YDELETE ALL\033X Transaction Records:</t>
 <t id="1223">%s Cr</t>
 <t id="1224">%s %s Cr</t>
 <t id="1225">No Reporting Entries Found:</t>
 <t id="1226">\033RDELETE MODE ACTIVE:\033X</t>
 <t id="1227">Delete Options:</t>
 <t id="1228">Delete \033YALL\033X</t>
 <t id="1229">Turn Individual Delete Mode %s:</t>
 <t id="1230">\033RON\033X</t>
 <t id="1231">\033GOFF\033X</t>
 <t id="1232">Sort by Corporation:</t>
 <t id="1233">Sort by Company:</t>
 <t id="1234">Corporate Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="1235">Company Transaction Report</t>
 <t id="1502">st.ex.Options.global.variable</t>
 <t id="1503">\033COptions:\033X</t>
 <t id="1505">Options Menu</t>
 <t id="1506">\033CAvailable Options:\033X</t>
 <t id="1508">Restore Defaults</t>
 <t id="1509">\033CReports:\033X</t>
 <t id="1510">\033CGeneral Options:\033X</t>
 <t id="1511">Only include known Sectors in Exchange?</t>
 <t id="1512">Only include known Exchange Stations?</t>
 <t id="1513">Only include Exchanges with Good Relations?</t>
 <t id="1514">Only allow Wares I have Notoriety to Buy?</t>
 <t id="1521">Open in Expanded View?</t>
 <t id="1530">\033CView Details of Shares Owned Menu:\033X</t>
 <t id="1540">\033CLocal Stock Exchange Menu:\033X</t>
 <t id="1550">\033CStock Exchange Buy / Sell Menu:\033X</t>
 <t id="1551">Pay Republic Brokerage Buy / Sell fee?</t>
 <t id="1552">If paying fee, use this percentage</t>
 <t id="1555">For testing purposes, actually use credits ?</t>
 <t id="1560">Select the \033CESC\033X key to \033RExit\033X without Saving Changes:</t>
 <t id="1561">\033CSave and Exit:\033X</t>
 <t id="1562">\033GSave\033X and \033RExit\033X:</t>
 <t id="1563">The following Options are available and can be set</t>
 <t id="1564">to your Preferences and \033GSaved\033X:</t>
 <t id="1567">Create Commodity Share \033GBuy \033C/ \033RSell\033X Report?</t>
 <t id="1568">Create Corporate Share \033GBuy \033C/ \033RSell\033X Report?</t>
 <t id="1569">Create Company Share \033GBuy \033C/ \033RSell\033X Report?</t>
 <t id="1570">Default Expanded View Details:</t>
 <t id="1571">Show Corporate Index if Expanded?</t>
 <t id="1572">Show Company Index if Expanded?</t>
 <t id="1573">\033CCorporate / Company Indexes Menu:\033X</t>
 <t id="1574">Limit Shares Available?</t>
 <t id="1575">Show Subtitle if Owned Shares Price Changes?</t>
 <t id="1577">Owned Shares Price Change Subtitles %s:</t>
 <t id="1578">Started</t>
 <t id="1579">Stopped</t>
 <t id="1580">\033CCommodities Index Menu:\033X</t>
 <t id="5001">Shareholdings</t>
 <t id="5002">Tradings</t>
 <t id="5003">Enterprises</t>
 <t id="5004">Industries</t>
 <t id="5005">Holdings</t>
 <t id="5006">Futures</t>
 <t id="5007">Technologies</t>
 <t id="5008">Advertising</t>
 <t id="5009">Research and Development</t>
 <t id="5010">Incorporated</t>
 <t id="5011">Ventures</t>
 <t id="5012">Marketing</t>
 <t id="5013">Consolidated</t>
 <t id="5014">Explorations</t>
 <t id="5015">Securities</t>
 <t id="5016">Tourism</t>
 <t id="5017">Transport</t>
 <t id="5018">Logistics</t>
 <t id="5019">Developments</t>
 <t id="5020">Acquisitions</t>
 <t id="5021">Space Dynamics</t>
 <t id="5022">Aerospace</t>
 <t id="5023">Custom Engineering</t>
 <t id="6010">Old Republic Acquisitions</t>
 <t id="10008">Weapons:</t>
 <t id="10009">Shields:</t>
 <t id="10010">Missiles:</t>
 <t id="10011">Energy Cells:</t>
 <t id="10012">Natural:</t>
 <t id="10013">Bio:</t>
 <t id="10014">Food:</t>
 <t id="10015">Minerals:</t>
 <t id="10016">Tech:</t>
 <t id="1020101">The Royal New Republic Kingdom has decreed that access to Stock Exchanges become available at the Trade Rank of Trader</t>
 <t id="1020206">Corporate Sector Trade Officials will grant access to Corporate Sector Stock Exchanges upon paying a modest administration fee of 10,000 Cr.</t>
 <t id="1020308">The Mandalorian family refuse to allow trading on their Stock Exchanges unless you have demonstrated your worth. A minimum Fight Rank of Enlisted is required</t>
 <t id="1020402">Rebel Trade Authorities have restricted access to the Stock Market to individuals who own at least one station in Rebel space</t>
 <t id="1020413">Imperial Trade Authorities have restricted access to the Stock Market to individuals who own at least one station in Imperial space</t>
 <t id="1020419">{1907,1020101}</t>
 <t id="1020517">{1907,1020308}</t>
 <t id="1020612">{1907,1020206}</t>
 <t id="1020702">The High Priest Duke has authorised individuals of CIS Notoriety Friend of Priest to gain access to the CIS Stock Exchanges</t>
 <t id="1020713">{1907,1020402}</t>
 <t id="1020808">{1907,1020402}</t>
 <t id="1020820">{1907,1020206}</t>
 <t id="1021001">The Old Republic, in co-operation with other clans, require you to prove your character and will allow access to their Stock Exchanges upon delivery of any of the following contraband, 7 Slaves, 14 Corellian Ale, or 4 Spice</t>
 <t id="1021007">{1907,1020101}</t>
 <t id="1021018">{1907,1021001}</t>
 <t id="1021019">{1907,1021001}</t>
 <t id="1021110">{1907,1021001}</t>
 <t id="1021204">{1907,1020206}</t>
 <t id="1021303">{1907,1020308}</t>
 <t id="1021410">{1907,1020702}</t>
 <t id="1021503">{1907,1020101}</t>
 <t id="1021518">{1907,1020101}</t>
 <t id="1021615">{1907,1020308}</t>
</page>
<page id="8387" title="al plugin information" descr="">
 <t id="2">Galaxy in Chaos Events</t>
 <t id="3">Galaxy in Chaos Misc. Scripts</t>
</page>
<page id="301266" title="Racenames" descr="Strings for the races">
 <t id="7">Khillik</t>
 <t id="18">Imperial</t>
 <t id="19">Old Republic</t>
 <t id="201">(textid 2xx = race abbreviation for shipnames like &quot;A. Buster&quot;)A.</t>
 <t id="202">B.</t>
 <t id="203">S.</t>
 <t id="204">P.</t>
 <t id="205">T.</t>
 <t id="206">X.</t>
 <t id="207">K.</t>
 <t id="208">Pi.</t>
 <t id="209">G.</t>
 <t id="211">E. R.</t>
 <t id="212">N. R.</t>
 <t id="213">F. R.</t>
 <t id="214">U.</t>
 <t id="215">R. 1</t>
 <t id="216">R. 2</t>
 <t id="217">R. 3</t>
 <t id="218">Ter.</t>
 <t id="219">Y.</t>
</page>
<page id="350017" title="Boardcomp. objects" descr="">
 <t id="15271">Terracorp HQ</t>
 <t id="15272">Terracorp Headquarters has made a significant contribution to the Rebel economy and has, in recent years, become a one-stop-shop for entrepreneurs equipping ships for a variety of tasks. Terracorp's strong mercantile base has allowed it to develop a formidable independent security arm, providing protection for its own and other companies' vessels. Julian Brennan, aka Julian Gardna, is a well-known former Terracorp employee.</t>
 <t id="15281">Sorosuub Corporation HQ(speak Oh-Tass)</t>
 <t id="15282">The Headquarters of Sorosuub serves not only as the centre of its corporate operations but also as a high-tech showroom for its cutting-edge ship technology. This imposing structure is a focal point for activity in the Sullust sector.</t>
 <t id="15321">Pike Syndicate HQ</t>
 <t id="15322">This station embodies the very essence of the Pike Syndicate organisation. This gleaming modern headquarters is the outer shell, concealing a corrupt, sly and manipulative core of pirates known for spice mining on the asteroid of Kessel and many more illegal activities.</t>
 <t id="15341">Mandal Hypernautics HQ</t>
 <t id="15342">Designed as the hub of their vast ship building and design empire, this station is the headquarters of the Mandal Hypernautics Corporation. This station coordinates all of Mandal hypernautics ship design and production enterprises.</t>
 <t id="16001">Orbital Shield Array</t>
 <t id="99700">SPHAT Beam</t>
 <t id="99704">DBY-827 Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="99705">DBY-827 Turoblaser Forge</t>
 <t id="99710">Proton Bomb</t>
 <t id="99711">The Proton Bomb is a a dumbfire adaption of the standard proton torpeedo in use by most bombers for ground targets. It is adapted for space combat where it sees a significantly faster fire rate in exchange for range and losing its guidance capabilities. Notorious for taking out capital ship shields and subsystems.</t>
 <t id="99712">Proton Bomb Forge</t>
 <t id="99713">This forge manufactures the Proton Bomb.</t>
 <t id="99716">Ancient Rapid-fire Dual Turbolaser Battery</t>
 <t id="99717">This turbolaser battery was equipped on ancient sith ships such as the Interdictor cruiser. It fired very quick and powerful shots, but suffered in accuracy. Who knew that letting your gunners get drunk could cost you a war.</t>
 <t id="99718">Ancient Rapid-fire Dual Turbolaser Battery Forge</t>
 <t id="99719">This ancient forge produces the equally ancient Rapid-fire Dual Turbolaser Battery.</t>
 <t id="99722">Superheavy Quad Ion Cannon</t>
 <t id="99723">This extremely heavy weapon was designed for Mon Cal ships to make it easier for them to disable Star Destroyers. It has quadrouple the damage output of the standard Heavy Ion Cannon and is capable of engaging at seige range at the expense of fire rate and energy usage.</t>
 <t id="99724">Superheavy Quad Ion Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="99725">This forge manufactures the Superheavy Quad Ion Cannon.</t>
 <t id="99726">Medium Bomber Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="99727">This model of laser cannon is a generic design produced by many companies by liscense on both sides of the Galactic Civil War. It is capable of dealing heavy damage to fighters, and is designed to be a bomber's last defense against enemy fighters where most bombers lack the agility to defend themselves otherwise. Great at taking out capital ship subsystems.</t>
 <t id="99728">Heavy Repeating Dual Turbolaser Cannon</t>
 <t id="99729">This laser was designed and implemented as a modification to many Republic ships after the Clone Wars to upgrade their firepower to modern standards. It is most notorious for being equipped as the primary battery on the Liberation, a Venator class Star Destroyer that serves with the Rebel Alliance, allowing it to outgun Imperial Star Destroyers.</t>
 <t id="99730">Heavy Repeating Dual Turbolaser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="99731">This forge manufactures the Heavy Repeating Dual Turbolaser Cannon.\n</t>
 <t id="99732">Capital Heavy Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="99733">This laser cannon is a generic weapon manufactured with liscense by many companies and has found itself in use on both sides of the Clone Wars and Galactic Civil War. It was designed to help capital ships screen fighters. It is lackluster as a point-defense weapon however, as it trades fire rate and turret slewing rate for damage output. Deceptively good damage dealer with great energy efficiency.</t>
 <t id="99734">Capital Heavy Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="99735">This forge manufactures the Capital Heavy Laser cannon.</t>
 <t id="99800">Siege Laser Array</t>
 <t id="99802">Siege Laser Array Forge</t>
 <t id="99900">Pulse-Charged Laser Cannon Forge</t>
 <t id="99965">Photon Beam Lance</t>
 <t id="99970">Positron Bombardment Cannon</t>
 <t id="99978">Omega Kyon Emitter</t>
 <t id="99979">Light Devastator Weapon\n\nThe Omega Kyon Emitter, is the latest technological discovery to hail from outside of the galaxy, being used by the OCV. That being said, not too much is known about this fantasy like weapon, other than that all ships that attempt to find any more information never make the round trip.</t>
 <t id="99980">Pulse-Charged Laser Cannon</t>
 <t id="99981">Medium Class Weapon\n\n\nSomeone decided that it would be a good idea to rig one of those Atgar14 laser tower emplacements onto a ship, and surprisingly it works.</t>
 <t id="99982">Alpha Kyon Autocannon</t>
 <t id="99983">Jump Beacon Factory</t>
 <t id="99985">Marauder Artillery Platform</t>
 <t id="99986">This Marauder cruiser has had its missile tubes replaced with extra lasers and its ammunition bays replaced with extra energy generation. It is best used as an artillery ship kept away from the frontlines.</t>
 <t id="99992">Siege Laser Array Forge</t>
 <t id="998001">Siege Class Weapon\n\nThe Siege Laser array is a development of superheavy turbolasers for capital ships produced by the Free Pammant Shipyards to give their products an extreme range advantage over contemporary designs by Kuat Driveyards. It is capasble of targeting enemies over 20 kilometers away.</t>
</page>
<page id="381000" title="Job names" descr="">
 <t id="101">(textid 1xx = race for shipnames like &quot;Rebel Buster&quot;)Rebel Alliance</t>
 <t id="102">Secforce</t>
 <t id="103">Mandalorian</t>
 <t id="104">Separatist Holdouts</t>
 <t id="105">Corporate Sector</t>
 <t id="10428">KDY Military Escort</t>
 <t id="10429">KDY Military</t>
 <t id="10430">Ice Transporter</t>
 <t id="10431">Holdout</t>
</page>
</language>
